(Penny:)walking around
with his metal detector.
(Amy:)If I were going to Hawaii,
(Amy:)I'd spend all my time
at the Keck Observatory.
(Amy:)Did you know that
the telescopes there have
(Amy:)better resolution
than the Hubble?
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Penny:)Want to go to Hawaii?
(knocking on door)
SHELDON: Ladies?
(knocks on door)
Ladies...
Ladies?
(Penny:)Come in.
(Sheldon:)Ladies.
(Penny:)What's up?
(Sheldon:)As you may know,
I've been experimenting
(Sheldon:)with elevated anxiety levels,
(Sheldon:)and I thought,
(Sheldon:)what better way
to increase my discomfort
(Sheldon:)than to subject myself
to an evening
(Sheldon:)of tasteless
uncensored crotch talk?
(Penny:)What exactly do you think
goes on here?
(Sheldon:)Well...
(Sheldon:)conversations that you wouldn't
be comfortable having
(Sheldon:)in front of the opposite sex.
(Sheldon:)You know, who has
the best cervix.
(Sheldon:)Which sanitary napkin
is all the rage right now.
(Sheldon:)Men's buttocks, and how you want
to pat and squeeze them.
(Bernadette:)We were talking
about Penny's job.